Dad, did you watch movies in those days?
Did you watch? I was a TFI
subscriber back then. Yes,
yes. Back then, your father used to
watch two or three movies a day. He did
n't even smoke cigarettes while watching movies.   In
those days, TFI movies were different, TFI
wars were different, and TFI wars were also
doing something different.
I started doing it when my hero and the opposite hero didn't have
any conflict, but we would create conflict and do it ourselves
.   When
our hero's movie came out, he would go to the first show on the first day.
What would he do if he couldn't find a ticket? He would buy it in bulk and
go to the cinema. That's how it all
went.